I can tolerate a lot,
我再能忍
but I shouldn't tolerate a woman
也不该接受一个女人
singing love songs
在我面前
to my fiancé
对着我的另一半
right in front of me.
唱情歌吧
Especially on my birthday.
还是在我的生日
That's just outrageous.
太过分了
A love that can't be made public
不能公开的爱情
is really difficult.
真的好难啊
You know how much I care about you.
你明知道我那么喜欢你
Do you really have to
你一定要拒我于
push me away?
千里之外吗
And you know very well
而且你心里很清楚
that without the backing of those
如果没有我手里的那些
major corporations
巨头企业
and listed companies from my networks,
和上市公司的支持
it would be tough for you to secure the
你想要晋升分行行长
position of the president of the branch.
也很难胜券在握
In this society, effort alone
这个社会不是空有努力
and talent aren't enough for success.
和能力就可以成功的
You have the talent,
你有能力
and I have the connections.
我有资源
As long as you stay by my side,
你只要跟我在一起
you can achieve
就可以得到
whatever you desire.
更多你想要的
I will achieve my goals
我想要的东西
on my own.
我会自己去拿
I don't need anyone's charity.
不需要别人的施舍
That was a bold statement.
你话说得好听
I can bring these people in
我可以带这些人来
to elevate you to a high position,
捧你上高位
but I can also take them away
我也可以把这些人带走
and let you fall to the bottom.
让你跌落谷底
That's what I'm capable of.
这就是我的能力
I shouldn't interfere with your choices.
你的选择我无权干涉
Still, for your information,
但是我还是要多说一句
Don't get too cocky.
不要太高看你自己
You know, Yuhui,
小唐你知道
those connections of yours
你的那些资源
give you an edge; that's for sure.
确实是你的优势
But I, Ji Yuheng,
但是我纪昱恒
have come this far
能走到今天这步
not because of you
靠的不是你
or anyone else.
也不是其他任何人
I'm not interested in your connections.
你的资源我不感兴趣
Whether you choose to stay or leave,
是走还是留
it's your call.
我不会左右你
As your supervisor,
之前我作为你的上司
there were things you didn't make public,
有些事情你不说破
and I merely reminded you
我也只是提醒你
to keep your expectations in check.
收起那份心
But now, with your
但是你现在这样
reckless behavior,
肆无忌惮地
I've got no choice but to tell you
我也只能告诉你
that my team
我这里
has no place for you.
容不下你
Nothing can stop me
我想要的东西
from getting what I want,
一定会得到
and you are part of that.
包括你
If we were to be together,
如果我们两个在一起
I'd be willing to leave Dairui for you.
我愿意为了你离开代瑞
We're just not right for each other;
我们不合适
and it's impossible for us to be together.
也不可能
Is it because of Tu Xiaoning?
就因为涂筱柠吗
In terms of education,
论学历
family background,
家世
and looks,
样貌
what does she have
她到底哪一点
that could compare to me?
能比得上我
And after all this time,
而且这么长时间了
I refuse to believe you have
我不相信你对我
no feelings for me whatsoever.
一丁点感觉都没有
The girl who first captured your attention
明明先走进你眼睛里的
was me.
那个人是我
Back in college,
上大学的时候
at the entrance of the first building,
在一教门口
we met for the very first time.
我们第一次见面
The way you looked at me was
你看我的眼神
genuinely affectionate and unmistakable.
是骗不了人的
From that moment on,
从那个时候起
you've held a special place in my heart.
你就一直在我心里了
I knew
我知道
you were different from the others.
你跟其他男生不一样
You didn't play video games,
你不打游戏
you didn't skip classes,
不逃课
you approach everything
做所有事情
with sincerity.
都认真
You're disciplined.
克制
You are exactly the lover I desire.
你就是我想要的人
And after all these years,
而且这么多年过去了
we still cross paths.
我们还能遇到
You're not married,
你没有结婚
and I'm still single.
我也还是单身
Shouldn't we
我们难道不应该
be together?
在一起吗
Are you finished, my junior?
说完了吗师妹
Honestly, aside from our bond as
其实我除了对你有师兄
senior and junior,
和师妹的同门情谊之外
I've never had
我对你没有过
any other feelings for you.
其他任何想法
Watch out for yourself.
你好自为之
Just because of Tu Xiaoning,
就因为涂筱柠
just because she's in the picture,
就因为她出现了
are you now going to deny
所以现在你就要否认
everything that happened between us?
过去的一切吗
Why does everything come to this?
我不明白到底为什么呀
What does she have that's better than me?
她到底哪点比我好
Is it because she's opportunistic,
就因为她会乘虚而入
she's skilled at maneuvering,
她会来事
and she's attuned to your desires?
她会投你所好是吗
Tu Xiaoning,
涂筱柠
you've just turned a year older.
你又长大了一岁
Could you please
你能不能做事
stop being so sneaky?
别这么见不得人啊
Hiding in the shadows like this,
你这样猫在暗处
that was really despicable.
我看不起你
I didn't mean to eavesdrop
我没有偷听你们俩
on your conversation.
讲话的意思
I was just passing by.
只是路过
I heard you call my name,
听到你叫我的名字
so I came out.
我才走出来
You two are now
你们两个现在
officially going public, aren't you?
一点都不避讳了是吗
Aren't you worried I'll head inside
你们不怕我现在过去
and tell everyone
告诉他们
what your relationship is?
你们俩是什么关系吗
You can do
你想怎么做
as you wish.
都随你
But today,
但是今天
I need to set the record straight.
我要澄清一件事情
In my relationship with Tu Xiaoning,
在我和涂筱柠的感情里
it has never been her
乘虚而入
who exploits opportunities
和投其所好的人
and caters to the other's desires.
从来都不是她
It's always been me.
是我
I fell for Tu Xiaoning
我对涂筱柠
at first sight.
是一见钟情
Let's go.
我们走
After all,
毕竟
this is your first birthday
是我们在一起以后
since we got together.
你第一个生日
It deserves to be celebrated.
还是要有点仪式感的
You just mentioned
你刚才说
that you fell for me at first sight.
你对我是一见钟情
I thought we were together
我本来以为
because we felt
我们两个是因为
a genuine connection
觉得合适
and decided to pursue a relationship.
才结婚谈恋爱的
This is quite unexpected.
我没想到
Long time no see.
好久不见啊
Tu Xiaoning.
涂筱柠
Is everything you just said true?
是真的吗
How could that possibly be?
那怎么会呢
What's there to doubt?
有什么不会的
I'm a normal guy,
我也是一个正常的男人
with my own feelings and desires.
也有七情六欲
Surely I can fall in love at first sight.
当然也会一见钟情了
And you know,
而且你也知道
I've always been
我这个人向来
very meticulous.
都很严谨的
Marriage is a serious matter;
婚姻大事
I wouldn't treat it lightly.
我不会当成儿戏
I wanted to register with you
我想和你领证
because I truly like you.
是因为我喜欢你
Then why didn't you
那你为什么
tell me sooner?
不早告诉我呢
I...
我
I was afraid.
我是怕
Afraid that at that time,
怕你那个时候
you wouldn't feel the same way.
没有这个心思
The candle is almost burnt out.
蜡烛快烧完了
Make a wish.
快许愿吧
I hope
我希望
that every birthday in the future
未来的每一个生日
will have Ji Yuheng by my side.
都有纪昱恒陪着我
♪All the little things about♪
所有关于
♪you mean more to me♪
你的点滴
♪than I ever imagined.♪
比想象中还在意
So happy, truly happy.
开心 开心
Fanggang.
赵哥
Let's go.
走啊
Let's head back and get another around.
咱回去接着
You guys go ahead.
你们先回去吧
I'm
我
still hungry.
没吃饱呢
I'll keep eating for a bit.
我接着吃点
I'll catch up with you guys shortly.
回去找你们一会儿
You're such a buzzkill; hurry up!
太扫兴了你 那你快点
Alright.
好
Come on.
快点
Hurry, OK?
快点啊
Let's move!
走
Hurry!
快点
Are you alright?
你行不行
I messed up.
我错了
I shouldn't have used water pistol on you.
我白天不该拿水泼你
Look, you've ignored me all day.
你看你都一天不理我了
I was wrong, seriously.
我真的知道错了
Don't be mad at me.
你别生我气了
You didn't eat
你看你一天
much today.
都没怎么吃东西
Let me get you some lamb.
我给你剃点羊肉
I'm not eating that.
我吃不了
It's too gamey.
膻
Don't shut me out!
不要不理我了呀
Hey,
不是
you talk too much!
你话怎么这么多
Let me tell you,
我跟你讲
I'll settle the score with you later.
我回去再找你算账
I won't be OK unless you
你回去不找我算账
settle the score with me later.
我还不答应
What are you...
你又干
Why are you back alone?
怎么一个人回来了
Where's Mr. Ji?
纪总呢
He probably went back to his room.
回房间了吧
Jing,
静姐
have a drink with me.
喝一杯
No, I'm good.
酒我就不喝了
I noticed you didn't drink earlier.
我刚才就发现你没喝酒
What's going on?
怎么
Are you on a sobriety kick?
戒酒了
Blah, blah, blah,
你收破烂的瞎吆喝
why are you talking so much?
你话怎么这么密呢
Get out of my face and go to sleep!
能不能滚回去睡觉
Get lost!
滚
Aye aye, ma'am!
好的
Did you already know
你是不是早就知道
what was going on between
纪昱恒
Ji Yuheng and Tu Xiaoning?
和涂筱柠的关系了
The first time we met,
我们两个第一次见面
was actually at
其实是在
an academic building
学校的
on campus.
教学楼前
I remember that day,
那天
the weather was particularly nice.
我记得天气特别好
I had just finished classes
我放了学
and was planning to go with my bestie
准备跟同学
to watch a theatrical play
一起去看一场
about a romantic story.
爱情话剧
Then he suddenly
然后他突然
appeared behind me.
出现在我身后
At that moment, I felt
那一刻我觉得
like time had stopped.
时间都停下来了
It felt like
全世界
the whole world was
就好像只有我跟他
just me and him.
我们两个人
So, thinking back,
这么说起来
I guess I fell for him
我好像对他
at first sight.
就是一见钟情
Then he told me
然后他突然跟我说
he had mistaken me for someone else,
他认错人了
and then he just walked away.
然后他就走了
But from that moment on,
但是从那个时候开始吧
I started to notice him.
我就开始注意到他了
And I came to know
我也就知道
how exceptional he is.
他到底有多优秀
I remember one year,
我记得有一年
during New Year's,
元旦的时候
our dorm held a gathering,
我们宿舍搞联谊
and everyone attended.
所有人都去了
Only he stayed behind
只有他一个人
in his room to work on his thesis.
留在宿舍里面写论文
Can you even believe that?
你敢相信吗
Not long after,
然后过了没多久
he became the first undergraduate student
他就成了他们那一届
in his class to publish
第一个
as the first author
以一作身份
in a
发表
core journal.
核心期刊的本科生
That's when I realized
然后我就觉得
this guy
这个男生
is truly exceptional.
真的是太优秀了
And then, I found
然后呢
myself falling for him even deeper.
我就更喜欢他了
So one time,
所以有一次呢
during PE class,
在体育课上
I mustered up my courage
我就
and asked him.
鼓起勇气
Yuheng,
师哥
what kind of girl do you like?
你喜欢什么样的女生
Someone with a high ponytail,
高马尾
and a cheerful laugh.
笑声爽朗
Then I thought the girl in our department
那我就在想当时我们系
who was known for her high ponytail
爱扎高马尾的女生
was none other than me.
就是我呀
So naturally,
那我理所应当
I thought he must be talking about me.
觉得那个人肯定就是我
I figured he was just
我觉得他可能只是
too shy to
太害羞了
express himself.
不敢表达
Then he suddenly
然后他就
went abroad,
到他突然出国
and I started working.
我工作
We didn't
我们就
see each other
很长一段时间
for a long time.
没有见到面
Until we met again
直到我们在代瑞
at Dairui.
再次遇到
I...
我
So later on,
所以我后来
I sometimes found myself wondering,
就有时候在想啊
he's been single for so long,
他单身那么久
could it be
哪怕
that even a little bit
一丁点
has something to do with me?
跟我有没有关系呢
Even if not,
即使是没有
then in terms of romantic relations,
那在感情方面
do I have a shot?
我是不是有胜算呢
It's actually ridiculous, you know?
就很可笑你知道吗
I have actually
其实是我自己
trapped myself.
把自己困住了
I've confined myself
我把自己困在了
to the fleeting glance
学生时代
I had of him during my student days.
对他的惊鸿一瞥里
This isn't affection,
这不是感情
but an obsession.
这是执念
Come on,
来
Tang Yuhui,
唐羽卉
it's been so long already.
时间都过了这么久了
Time to wake up.
该醒醒了
Tang Yuhui,
唐羽卉
you're an outstanding girl.
你那么优秀
It's just relationships;
感情而已
why trap yourself?
何必困住自己呢
Take care of yourself.
好好地
You're awake.
醒了
I brought you some breakfast.
给你拿了一些早餐
What is this?
这是什么啊
A birthday gift for you.
送你的生日礼物
Do you like it?
喜欢吗
I love it.
喜欢
I also got you a gift.
我也给你买了一个礼物
Look!
看
It's exactly the same!
一模一样
Why did you want to
怎么突然想着
give me a gift all of a sudden?
送我礼物啊
Mr. Zhao said
小赵哥说
a man should have a decent watch.
男人要有块像样的手表
I've been managing our income for so long
我管钱管了这么久
and haven't bought you anything.
没给你买过什么东西
So I thought,
就想着
taking this opportunity,
借着这个机会
I'd buy you a watch.
给你买块手表
And our tastes
而且我们俩的眼光
are exactly the same!
一样啊
Matching couple watches.
情侣款
Aren't they too similar?
这是不是太像了
They're obviously matching ones.
一看就是情侣款
Then how can we
那我们俩
wear them together?
怎么一起戴出去啊
Well,
那
how about this:
要不
you wear yours most of the time,
平时就你戴着
and I'll find chances
我找机会
to wear mine secretly.
偷偷戴着
How does that sound?
好不好
You are the boss.
都听你的
Why are you smiling?
怎么突然笑起来了
I just remembered
我突然想起来
the first time I rode in your car,
我第一次坐你车的时候
you played the same song.
你放的也是这首歌
So you've been having
原来你从那个时候
feelings for me since then?
就喜欢我啦
Nice acting, Mr. Ji.
演技不错啊纪先生
I couldn't tell at all.
根本看不出来
Congratulations.
恭喜你啦
You've landed
谈下来惟纪
such a big project like Weiji.
这么大的一个项目
Regarding our earnout agreement,
咱们俩的对赌协议
we should have already doubled the
让一部的业绩翻一倍
performance of our team by now, right?
应该已经达成了吧
How do you know?
你怎么知道
Did you calculate it in secret?
偷偷算过啊
Yeah, I did.
算过了
The Weiji deal
惟纪公司的业绩
plus the 800 million deposits
加上之前
from the government,
政府的八亿存款
let alone doubling,
别说翻一倍了
it could even triple!
翻两倍都能翻过去了吧
There are still five months left
离对赌协议结束
until our agreement ends.
还有五个月
I haven't even achieved
我这五千万的业绩
half of my 50 million goal.
还没完成一半呢
Do you need any help?
要不要帮帮你啊
No, I'm good.
不要
I can handle it myself.
我自己可以的
Every bit of my performance
我的每一分业绩
needs to be earned fairly and squarely.
都要清清白白的
I can do it myself.
我自己可以
Alright, Ms. Tu,
好了 涂小姐
we've arrived at your destination.
目的地到了
I wish you all the best
祝今天的项目
with this project.
一切都顺利
Thank you, Mr. Ji,
谢谢纪先生
for being my chauffeur.
给我当了专车司机
I'm going in.
走了
Go get them.
去吧
Xiaoning!
筱柠
What's wrong?
怎么了
Good luck!
加油啊
Go for it!
去吧
I'm going!
走了
So, you've made up your mind.
想好了
Yes.
当然
It's been a pleasure working with you.
很荣幸能够共事数月
I wish you all the best in the future.
也祝你前路顺遂
That should be
这话
my wish for you.
应该我祝你才是吧
After all, once I leave here,
毕竟我离开这儿之后
the future looks promising for me.
前途还是一片坦荡
But you'll face
可是你要面临的问题
quite a few challenges.
可不少
I still need to thank you for
我跟小涂的事情
keeping my relationship
还是要谢谢你
with Xiaoning a secret.
替我们保密了
Secrets always
常在河边走
come out in the end.
哪能不湿鞋呢
Anyway, your relationship
反正你们的事情
will eventually be found out.
早晚都会被他们知道
Why should I be the bad guy?
我何必做这个坏人呢
We should avoid embarrassing ourselves.
江湖留一线吗
We might still have the opportunity
说不定之后跟纪总
to work together in the future.
还有合作的机会
Looking forward to it.
期待
Yuheng,
师哥
ten years ago,
十年前
when you stopped me
在一教门口
at the entrance of the first building,
你叫住我的时候
were you trying to get to know me, or
是想认识我
did you really mistake me for someone else?
还是真的认错人了
Back then,
那时候
you had a high ponytail,
你扎着一个高马尾
and from behind,
从背影上看
you looked a lot like the girl
很像我高中时候
I liked in high school.
喜欢的女孩
So that girl was...
所以那个人是
Tu Xiaoning.
涂筱柠
So you've liked
所以你从那个时候
her since...
就已经
I started liking her
从高中的时候
back in high school.
我开始喜欢她
All these years, it's always been her.
这么多年一直是她
Only her.
也只有她
It seems that
看来
since I first met you,
从我认识你的时候开始
I've already lost my shot.
我就已经没有机会了
As I thought,
果然
it wasn't my problem.
不是我的问题
It's a shame
很遗憾
that I can't be
不能跟我的白月光
with my "Mr. Ideal."
走到最后
I wish you
那就祝你
all the best.
得偿所愿
Thank you.
谢谢
Actually, I'm not much different from you.
其实我和你没什么不同
I'm just a bit luckier.
只不过我更幸运一点
I got a second chance
能拥有和自己爱的人
to be with the one I love.
在一起的第二次机会
Xiaoning,
筱柠
I must get promoted to the president.
我必须完成行长竞聘
To give our relationship
给我们的感情
more confidence
更多的底气
and a backup plan.
和退路
If in the end,
如果最后
I don't want this child,
我不想要这个孩子
he'll probably come to haunt me.
他十有八九会来纠缠
It's already 21 million.
两千一百万了
There's still 29 million left.
还剩两千九百万
I'll work harder.
努努力
With a bit of luck,
运气好的话
there's hope.
很有希望
Why are you
还有工夫
still working?
还有心思工作
Hey, I'm...
干什么 我
Hey, don't touch my desktop.
别动
I'm revising the contract!
我在 我在改合同
Look at this.
你看
Dairui's heartthrob, Ji Yuheng,
代瑞男神纪昱恒
who will he end up with?
花落谁家
Xiaoning,
小涂
come on!
来 来 来
Reading gossips at work
早晨上班的时候
in the morning...
看这个
That's huge!
太劲爆了
Who is it?
谁啊
The boss's girlfriend.
领导女朋友
You idiot!
说啥呢
Xiaoning was asking,
小涂问的是
who the boss' girlfriend is.
领导的女朋友是谁
How would I know?
我哪儿知道
You stupid...
你
But according to what it says here,
但是看这个描述啊
they were really
那是真真实实
hugging each other.
抱在一起了
So sweet!
可甜蜜呢
In a trench coat.
穿风衣
Has class? Of course!
气质不错那还用说吗
Our boss has great taste.
咱们领导眼光那是好
Of course.
那肯定
Sometimes,
网上的东西
you can't believe
有时候不能
everything you read on the internet.
不能全信
Look, it's all clear here.
你看 说得多清楚啊
It's not a celebrity or an internet star.
又不是什么明星网红
Enough, enough.
好了 好了
Stop gossiping.
别八卦了
Go back to your work!
赶紧该干吗干吗去
Miss Rao,
饶经理
I was...
我正
What's the hurry?
赶着投胎啊你
Eh,
那个
look,
你看
this contract...
这合同
There was a post online,
网上出来一个帖子
saying that
说
there was a mysterious girl...
一个神秘女子
Did you see the post online?
网上的帖子你看到了吗
Someone saw us hugging.
有人看到我们拥抱了
Don't worry.
别担心
The one who posted it only saw from afar
发帖的人只是远远看到
that you were wearing a trench coat,
你穿了件风衣
but they didn't see your face,
没看清具体样貌
nor did they take a photo.
也没来得及拍照
Good then.
那还好
Where is Yuhui?
小唐到哪儿去了
She still hasn't shown up yet.
怎么到现在都没出现
Fanggang,
老赵
come here for a moment.
过来一下
Okay.
好
I'll go sound it out for you.
我去帮你探探口风
Do you think
你说
this mysterious woman
这个神秘女子
might be Yuhui?
会不会是小唐
Has class,
气质佳
wears a trench coat.
穿风衣
Doesn't Yuhui wear a trench coat?
小唐穿风衣吗
Plus, yesterday,
而且赵哥
Fanggang went over it with me.
昨天给我捋了一下
I'll go back to work then.
那我先去忙了
Enough.
行啦
Stop gossiping.
别八卦了
The boss said that
领导说了
it was his fiancé.
那是他未婚妻
His fiancé?
未婚妻
The boss has a fiancé?
领导有未婚妻了吗
Mr. Ji has a fiancé!
纪总有未婚妻了
What?
这
When did this happen?
什么时候的事儿
Why haven't I heard about it?
我怎么没听说过呢
My goodness!
我的天呢
You work with
你们这平时
Mr. Ji everyday.
天天跟纪总一块工作
And now, suddenly he's got
这突然出了个
this flashy girlfriend,
这么高调的女朋友
you've never heard anything?
一点风声都没有
No.
没有
Our boss is really good at
我们领导的保密工作呀
keeping it a secret.
做的是这个
And they never call
平时也不接电话
or text each other?
发个信息什么的
If this girl drops her boyfriend off
按理说这女的一大早
at work this early in the morning,
专门送男朋友来上班
they must be very clingy with each other.
平时应该挺腻歪的
What boyfriend?
什么男朋友
He's her fiancé.
人家是未婚夫
Right, right, right.
对 对 对
Her fiancé.
未婚夫
She's dropping her fiancé off at work.
送未婚夫来上班
Maybe this woman
说不准这女的她
works in this very building!
她就在这栋楼上班呢
Maybe it's the one
十二楼那个
who works in food and beverage marketing.
做餐饮营销的
Or the doctor from that
要不就是新开那家
newly opened stomatology hospital.
口腔医院的医生
I don't think it's neither of them.
我觉得都不是
The enemy
敌人
is within.
就在内部
I've long heard about him and Tang Yuhui,
刚走那唐羽卉啊
the one that just got transferred.
我早就听人说过他俩了
They studied together in university.
大学的时候就师兄妹
Maybe they've been together for a while.
说不定人俩早谈上了
Don't talk nonsense.
你可别瞎说啊
There's nothing
我们老大
between our boss and Tang Yuhui.
跟小唐可是清清白白的
Don't spread such rumors.
别瞎传
Not necessarily.
那可不一定啊
If there's truly nothing,
要没什么事的话
why did Yuhui leave?
小唐好好地干吗要走
Don't spread such rumors.
别瞎传啊
Xiaoning.
小涂
Xiaoning, this is the second floor.
小涂二楼
We're not arrived yet.
没到
Have a glass of milk.
喝杯牛奶
Why did you tell Fanggang
你怎么就跟小赵哥
that you were engaged?
说你订婚了呢
Now
现在
they're all talking
他们都在议论
about this.
这件事情
Instead of letting them gossip,
与其让他们议论纷纷
we might as well
还不如咱们
just admit it openly.
大大方方去承认呢
There will be less such comments
以后这样的话
in the future this way.
也能少一点
But,
可是
everyone is very curious now.
大家现在探索欲满满的
What if they find out?
要是被发现了怎么办呢
Okay now,
好了
don't worry.
放心吧
The bank doesn't survive
银行呢也不是靠
on gossip and rumors.
打听这些八卦吃饭的
We're all busy with work.
干业绩都来不及
Who's really
谁还真能
got the time to
七乘二十四小时地
watch my every move 24/7?
盯着我看呀
It'll be fine once it blows over.
等热度过去就好了
Today was my fault.
今天也怪我
What do we do in the future?
以后怎么办呀
I, I shouldn't have
我 我就不应该
let myself go and hugged you.
情不自禁地过去抱你
I should have held it back.
我应该忍住的
From now on,
以后
I can't use the hair tie anymore,
头绳也系不了了
nor can I wear the trench coat.
风衣也穿不了了
Most importantly,
最主要的是
I just bought that trench coat today!
那风衣是我今天刚买的
Isn't that perfect then?
那不正好吗
You can buy some more
趁这个机会
with this opportunity.
还能多买几件
No.
不好
I thought that
本来以为
with Tang Yuhui gone,
走了个唐羽卉
we have defused a ticking time bomb.
算是拆了个定时炸弹
Who would have thought that
结果呢
she was not the real threat.
谁能想到是个哑炮
How did it go with the Jian Branch?
集安分行那边怎么样
Could you get
行长的人选
the president position?
有希望吗
I thought since I got the Weiji Group,
原本拿下了惟纪公司
it would have been a sure thing.
应该是十拿九稳
But unexpectedly,
但是没想到国外
a few candidates came back from abroad.
回来了几个来竞聘的
They say their qualifications
据说是资历
and abilities are quite impressive.
和能力也不错
I guess the head office leaders
我估计总行的领导
would probably want to
应该是想
take a comprehensive look at all options
综合考量一下
before making
然后再做出
the best choice.
最优选
Now it's the time for us
越是在这个时候吧
to be extra careful.
我们越是要注意
In our bank,
在我们行
office romances are definitely
办公室恋情
not something that
确实是
should be brought into the open.
拿不上桌面的一件事情
So,
所以
if they find out about us,
如果我们被发现了
it could affect
就会影响
the leaders' judgement of you.
领导对你的判断
We can't let them find out about us,
这个时候
especially not now.
千万不能被他们发现
Especially with things like this,
尤其像这种事情
once one person finds out,
一旦被一个人知道
it will spread quickly,
一传十十传百
and soon everyone will know.
很快大家伙就都知道了
Here's what we'll do.
这样
From tomorrow,
从明天开始上班
I'll take the subway to work.
我坐地铁
And
然后
in the office, if there's no work-related
在单位里没什么事
issues, I will leave you alone.
我也不过去招惹你
We'll see after this period.
等度过这段时间再说
Okay.
好
However,
不过呢
you don't have to
你也不用
feel this much pressure.
这么大的心理压力
No matter what
不管是出现
bad situation arises,
什么坏的情况
I have a solution for it.
我都有应对的方案
What solution?
你应对什么呀
It's still better if they don't find out.
还是不要被发现最好
Okay.
行
I'll listen to you.
听你的
Why aren't you speaking to me?
怎么不理我呀
Say something, please.
说句话嘛祖宗
I don't want to talk today.
今天不想说话
Go back to your place.
你先回你那儿吧
I'm not going.
我不走
Didn't we say at the resort that
咱不是在度假村说好了
we'll settle the score after we get back?
回来找我算账的吗
We're not doing that anymore?
不算了
I'm not in the mood, forget it.
心情不好不算了
Wait,
不是
what happened exactly?
你到底怎么啦
Why are you sticking to me
不是你怎么像
like a piece of gum
狗皮膏药似的
that I can't shake off?
黏上了甩都甩不掉啊
My chance of being alone
我不能无缘无故
with my girlfriend can't just
被剥削掉跟女朋友
be taken away without any reasons.
单独相处的机会啊
Sticking?
黏
That's the first step.
也得先黏上再说
Tell me,
你跟我说说
what's going on with you?
你到底怎么了
Why aren't you talking to me
怎么突然
all of a sudden?
对我爱搭不理的
How annoying you are!
你看你那个烦人劲
Sometimes I just
我隔三差五
want to be alone, is that not allowed?
想清静清静还不行吗
Sure.
行
Giving each other
偶尔给彼此一些
some personal space sometimes
私人的情绪空间
can help the relationship.
有助于感情的稳定
I understand.
我懂
But,
但是
you still
饭
need to eat.
还是要吃的
Or
要不然啊
it's not good to your stomach.
对胃不好
I made your favorite, stir fried noodles
我做了你最爱吃的
with shredded pork and egg.
鸡蛋肉丝炒面
Here.
来
If he were to be a father,
要是做爸爸的话
he probably
他应该
would be
也是个
a responsible and great one.
负责任的好爸爸吧
Give it.
拿来吧
Slow down.
慢点吃啊
You're laughing!
笑了
You're happy now?
高兴了
Actually,
其实
today I...
我今天
As long as you're happy.
高兴就行
I was really frustrated.
这可把我憋死了
Who do you think
你说
Yuheng's fiancé
老纪的未婚妻
really is?
到底是什么人啊
Half a day later
过去半天了
you're still thinking about this?
你还琢磨这事呢
So mysterious.
这神神秘秘的
I'm so curious!
搞得人心痒痒
But I've already had it figured out.
不过我都已经想好了啊
Next time
下次
when I'm at a dinner party with Yuheng,
等老纪的饭局
I'll take him home
我趁他喝多了
when he's drunk.
我借机送他回家
This way,
这样
I can see
我就能看到
who she really is.
我弟妹是谁了
What do you think?
怎么样
Am I smart or what?
够机智吧
Smart. Just don't be
机智你到时候
too surprised when that happens.
别吓个半死就行
Not possible.
那不可能
Next week?
下周
No, not next week.
下周不行
The week after that.
下下周
That week the park is looking for investments,
下下周园区招商
there'll definitely be a dinner party.
肯定有饭局
Why don't you have a bite too,
要不你也吃两口
and shut your mouth!
把你那个嘴给我堵上
I made this for you!
这是我给你做
Why did you leave?
你怎么又走了呢
Wait for me!
你等等我
Seducing someone's husband
敢不要脸地
this shamelessly.
勾引别人老公
Do you dare to show your face?
怎么不敢出来呀
Come out!
出来
And let all your colleagues see
让你们同事都看看
what kind of person you really are!
看看你是个什么东西
Is it you?
是不是你
who seduced my husband?
勾引我们家老邢
What's happening?
什么情况
Who is it?
谁呀
Section two's
拓展二部
-Is it you? -Mr. Xing's wife,
是不是你 邢总的太太
said someone's having an affair
说是有人在单位
with Mr. Xing in the office.
跟邢总乱搞男女关系
She's here to catch them!
当面捉奸来了
And Mr. Xing?
邢总呢
Why isn't he here?
怎么还不出来
What if the situations escalates?
这要闹出大事怎么办
Mr. Xing must be hiding far away.
邢总肯定躲得远远的
Who dares to come out
这种情况
and confront directly in this situation?
谁还敢正面出来刚
Bastard!
臭男人
Is it you
是不是你
who seduced Mr. Xing?
勾引我们家老邢
Is it you?
你吗
Did you seduce my husband?
是不是你们勾引我老公
No, no, no.
不 不 不
Is it you?
是不是你们
Then do you know who it was?
那你们知不知道是谁
Who is it? What?
谁呀怎么着
No one would say anything?
都不说话是吧
Did you seduce my husband?
是不是你们勾引我老公
What's happening?
什么情况
This early in the morning,
大清早
it's like a market here.
吵得跟菜市场似的
Section Two's Mr. Xing's wife.
拓展二部邢总的太太
Mr. Xing's wife?
邢总太太
I understand.
明白了
Eh, excuse me.
那个不好意思啊
It's work hours now,
现在是上班时间
can't you not...
您能不能别在我们
I know.
我知道了
Look at how you're dressed.
看你这穿衣打扮
You must be a slut!
一看你就是狐狸精
It must have been you
就是你
who seduced Mr. Xing!
勾引我们家老邢吧
Are you sure I
你确定我
seduced Mr. Xing?
勾引你们家老邢
Look at you,
你说你
dressed that slutty for work!
你上班穿得这么风骚
You don't look like a decent woman at all!
一看就不是正经人哪
You're the decent one then.
我不正经您正经
Calling someone a slut
大清早的
randomly
在我们公司门口
in front of our company
随便拉一个人
this early in the morning,
就骂人家狐狸精
are you a decent person?
您是正经人吗
Who are you calling indecent?
你说谁不正经
What do you want?
你干吗
Let go!
松手
I already called the police!
我已经报警了
Who are you calling indecent?
说谁不正经
Let go!
放手
He's hitting me! He's hitting me!
打人了 打人了
I see now!
我是看明白了
You two are having an affair!
你们俩有一腿吧
Did you all see?
大家看见了吗
Did you see?
看见没有
It's this woman!
就是这女的
Texting my husband
天天大半夜的
in the middle of the night everyday!
就给我们家老邢发信息
Talking about love and stuff!
说什么情呀爱呀的
All those shameless words!
都是那些不要脸的词
Shut up!
闭嘴
What are you talking about?
你胡说什么呢你
Why would I shut up?
我闭什么嘴我
Isn't she dressed like that
她穿成这样
to seduce men?
不就是为了勾引人吗
You only like other people's men, huh?
就看别人家男人好是吧
Do other people's men
别的男人
spend money on you?
都给你钱花是吗
Without men
没了男人
you can't live anymore, is that it?
你活不起吧你
She's free
她想怎么打扮
to dress however she wants!
是她自己的自由
It has nothing to do with you!
跟你没有任何关系
It's not wrong for anyone
任何人想展现
to show off their beauty.
自己的美都不是错
You
你
have no right to slander her!
没资格诋毁她
All these years
这些年
she's been working so hard.
她兢兢业业地工作
She's as good as anyone else!
能力不比任何人差
Certainly better than your husband!
更不比你老公差
She has had plenty of
她的客户里
wealthy and influential clients,
有钱有地位的多的是
but she's always been very professional.
她从来没有公私不分
She has never had any
跟任何人有过
inappropriate relationships with anyone!
不正当的关系
And she'd never be into your husband!
更不可能瞧上你老公
Moreover,
还有
she can't live without men?
她没有离了男人活不了
She's been living on her own independently
她一个人生活这么多年
all these years
过得非常独立
and has taken good care of herself.
把自己照顾得很好
It's not your place
轮不到你在这儿
to judge her here.
说三道四
You listen up,
你听清楚了
from now on,
从现在开始
if you insult her
如果你再有一句
even once,
侮辱她的话
I'll start recording
我立刻录音
and then call the police.
然后报警
Did you hear me?
听明白了吗
You know her pretty well.
你了解得挺透彻呀
What,
怎么着
are you her man?
你是她男人哪
Yes,
对
I'm her boyfriend.
我是她男朋友
The bank knows
你和饶静的事
about you and Jing.
行里知道了
One of you
你们俩
has to be transferred.
得调离一个
I've thought about it carefully.
我仔细考虑过了
I won't get transferred.
不准备调职
If I get transferred to another city,
要是调去别的市的话
Jing will be here
饶静又要
all alone.
一个人在这里
I'd rather quit.
我还是准备辞职
What are your plans
你跟饶经理
with Miss Rao for the future?
未来有什么打算啊
I'm not sure
她吗
about her,
我拿不准
but I definitely won't let go.
但我肯定不会放手
It's okay.
没事
You don't need to worry.
你也不用为难
I'll keep an eye for you
我也帮你留意一下
and see if there's
看市里
any suitable job for you in the city.
有没有合适的职位
Jing,
静姐
the boyfriend you were talking about
你之前说那些男朋友
before was Fanggang?
就是小赵哥呀
Fanggang's girlfriend
赵哥找的嫂子
is actually Jing!
竟然是静姐
If they two get together,
他俩搁一块
wouldn't they fight
那不是奥特曼
all the time?
打小怪兽
Behind all the conflicts,
打的全是情
it's all love.
骂的全是爱
Let's go.
走
Let's get some air.
透透气 透透气
All these dramas this early in the morning
一大早上就经历这一遭
is making me nauseous.
搞得我直犯恶心
I want to throw up.
想吐
Wait, Jing.
不对静姐
Your stomach is always upset
你最近吧
recently.
老是胃不舒服
It's still uncertain
你跟小赵哥的事
for you and Fanggang.
还没下定论
Let's put it aside for now.
咱先放一边
Let me go with you to the hospital.
我陪你去趟医院吧
Let's go do a check-up.
咱检查一下
It's not okay if your stomach's always upset.
胃老不舒服可不行
Stop looking.
别看了
I'm not carrying Nezha.
姐怀的又不是哪吒
It's not been long, it doesn't show yet.
这多长时间
*Nezha is a deity in Chinese folklore, his mom carried him for 3 and a half years.
显现不出来
Still looking.
还看
It really doesn't show yet.
确实什么都看不出来
I,
那
I'm just happy for you.
我就是替你高兴嘛
And Fanggang?
小赵哥呢
He must be really happy.
乐坏了吧
I didn't tell him.
我又没告诉他
Why?
为啥
These
这些
are the information about my clients.
都是我的客户资料
After I'm gone,
我走之后
they're all yours.
客户都留给你
These all belong to
这些也都是
Section One.
拓展一部的底子
If I bring them with me,
我要带走
it wouldn't be right to Yuheng.
太对不起老纪了
You're quitting?
你要辞职啊
Everyone knows about us now,
事情既然都已经闹开了
one of us has to be transferred.
咱俩势必得调走一个
I've seen enough
干了这么多年
discrimination against women
也看了不少
in the workplace these years.
职场对女性的偏见
If we start all over again
要是咱们这个年纪
at your age,
再从头开始
other banks
别的行
will surely
少不了
give you problems about
为婚育问题
marriage and having kids.
难为你
So you can't be transferred.
所以你不能调走
Plus when I pursued you,
而且追你的时候
I've already thought it through.
我都已经想好了
If someday
如果哪一天
they found out about us,
我俩的事被捅开了
and I broke up with you,
我要和你分手
or
或者
be a coward,
当缩头乌龟
I'm not a real man.
那我就不是男人
I should just leave you in peace then.
我趁早别来祸害你
They wanna transfer me to another city,
行里想把我调去别的市
but I don't want you to be alone.
但我不想你一个人
I'd rather quit.
我宁可辞职
What?
怎么了
There's something I didn't tell you.
我有件事没告诉你
I'm pregnant.
我怀孕了
Why are you still up?
怎么不睡觉
I'm turning off the light.
过来关灯了
Go back to sleep now.
快睡吧